A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 11, Accession 2022:039 FA1863
Rockefeller Archive Center
- The Phillips Collection - Jacob Lawrence Micro-Website, 2014-2019 (Box 36, Folder 237)
- Princeton University - Tibet Site Seminar, 2005-2019 (Box 37, Folder 238)
- Princeton University Art Museum - "Clarence White and His World: The Art and Craft of Photography, 1895-1925" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2021 (Box 37, Folder 239)
- Project Pericles - D4D on the Road Workshops, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 240)
- Public Art Fund - Liz Glynn: Opera House Sculpture Installation, 2016-2018 (Box 37, Folder 241)
- Public Radio International - Whose Century Is It?, 2015-2017 (Box 37, Folder 242)
- Public Radio International - Religion and International Affairs Coverage, The World, 2014-2017 (Box 37, Folder 243)
- Pulitzer Center on Crisis Reporting - Religion in Global Affairs and Universities, 2016-2019 (Box 38, Folder 244)
- Pulitzer Center on Crisis Reporting - Global Religious Issues, 2012-2020 (Box 38, Folder 245)
- Purdue University - Religion and Society in China Digital Project, 2013-2017 (Box 38, Folder 246-247)
- Queens Museum - "Mel Chin: All Over the Place" Exhibition and Catalog, 2017-2019 (Box 38, Folder 248)
- RAND Corporation - Religion, Conflict, and Stability in the Former Soviet Union, 2015-2018 (Box 38, Folder 249)
- Refugee Studies Centre, University of Oxford - Forced Migration Review, 2012-2016 (Box 39, Folder 250)
- Americans for Oxford - Forced Migration Review, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 251)
- Religions for Peace - Advancing a Moral Alliance among the World's Religions for an Integral Ecology, 2017-2018 (Box 39, Folder 252)
- Research Foundation of City University of New York - Bali 1928: Restoration and Repatriation of the Earliest Music Recordings and Films in Bali, 2015-2017 (Box 39, Folder 253)
- Rice University - Southeast Asia Fellowship, Transnational Asia Research Initiative, Chao Center for Asian Studies, 2015-2017 (Box 39, Folder 254)
- Rubin Museum of Art - Tibetan Art History, 2014-2017 (Box 40, Folder 255)
- Rutgers University Foundation - Diversifying Media Leadership: Identifying the Real Problems and Promoting Best Practices, 2015-2017 (Box 40, Folder 256)
- Saint Vincent College - Textile Database and Research Collection, 2015-2019 (Box 40, Folder 257)
- San Francisco Museum of Modern Art - "Bruce Conner: It's All True" Exhibition and Catalog, 2015-2018 (Box 40, Folder 258)
- Sarus - Myanmar-Bangladesh Exchange Program, 2014-2019 (Box 40, Folder 259)
- Seamen's Church Institute - Gulf Coast Harbor Missionaries, 2005-2007 (Box 40, Folder 260)
- Shaker Museum, Mount Lebanon - Electronic Catalog of Permanent Collection, 2016-2019 (Box 41, Folder 261-262)
- Shanghai Institute for International Studies - Chinese Think-Tanks and United States-China Relations Training Programs, 2006-2018 (Box 41, Folder 263)
- Sheldon Museum of Art - Digitization of American Works in Permanent Collection, 2014-2020 (Box 41, Folder 264)
- Silliman University - Applied Ethics Program, 2013-2019 (Box 41, Folder 265)
- Smithsonian Institution - "One Thing: Vietnam, Art, and America's Wars, 1965-1975" Exhibition and Catalog, 2017-2021 (Box 41, Folder 266)
- Smithsonian Institution - Redwick Gallery's American Craft and Decorative Art Collection, 2014-2017 (Box 41, Folder 267)
- Social Science Research Council - The Immanent Flame, 2015-2017 (Box 42, Folder 268)
- Social Science Research Council - 2014 Annual Association of Asia Studies Conference, Philadelphia, 2013-2018 (Box 42, Folder 269)
- Social Science Research Council - New Dissertation Workshop Model for the Study of Asia, 2011-2013 (Box 42, Folder 270-271)
- Society of Women Engineers - Electronic Compendium of SWE's Literature Reviews, 2009-2010 (Box 42, Folder 272)
- Southern Alleghenies Museum of Art - Update Database System, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 273)
- Socrates Sculpture Park - Exhibition and Programming Activities, 2016-2018 (Box 42, Folder 274)
- Henry L. Stimson Center - Ethnic Reconciliation in Northern Myanmar and the Peace Process, 2015-2018 (Box 43, Folder 275)
- Storm King Art Center - Oral History and Archives Program, 2014-2019 (Box 43, Folder 276)
- Studio Museum in Harlem - Creation of Studio Museum Archives, 2016-2021 (Box 43, Folder 277)
- Studio Museum in Harlem - Senior Archivist, 2016-2021 (Box 43, Folder 278)
- Syracuse University - Scholarly Exchange Program, North Korea, South Korea, China, and the United States, 2004-2018 (Box 43, Folder 279)
- Tanenbaum Center for Interreligious Understanding - Diplomatic Engagement with Religiously Motivated Peacemakers, 2016-2018 (Box 43, Folder 280)
- Tate Modern - "Soul of a Nation: Art in the Age of Black Power" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2021 (Box 44, Folder 281)
- Teach for China - United States-China Fellows Program, 2012-2019 (Box 44, Folder 282-283)
- Texas Tech Foundation, Inc. - Vietnam-United States Relations Symposium, Hanoi, 2010-2019 (Box 44, Folder 284)
- Trinity College - Anthology of American Literature, 2000-2017 (Box 44, Folder 285)
- Tufts University - Religious Claims, Nationalism, and Human Suffering, 2011-2017 (Box 45, Folder 286-287)
- Unicode, Inc. - Incorporate Asian Scripts into International Encoding Standards, 2015-2019 (Box 45, Folder 288)
- United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Tunghai University, Taiwan and Chung Chi College, and Chinese University of Hong Kong, 2013-2019 (Box 45, Folder 289)
- United Nations Association of the United States of America - United States-China Policy Dialogue on Global Security, 2001-2017 (Box 45, Folder 290)
- United States-Indonesia Society - Survey of Indonesian Studies in the United States, 2008-2017 (Box 45, Folder 291)
- University of California, Berkeley - "Repentant Monk: Illusion and Disillusion in the Art of Chen Hongshou" Exhibition, 2017-2019 (Box 46, Folder 292-293)
- University of California, Berkeley - Handbook of East and Southeast Asian Archaeology, 2014-2019 (Box 46, Folder 294)
- University of California, Berkeley - Women in Islamic Cultures Public Outreach, 2011-2017 (Box 46, Folder 295-296)
- University of California, Irvine - Humanities Out There Public Fellows Program Expansion, 2016-2018 (Box 47, Folder 297)
- University of California, Irvine - Religion and Humanitarianism in Africa, 2014-2019 (Box 47, Folder 298)
- University of California, Irvine - Religions in Diaspora and Global Affairs, 2012-2018 (Box 47, Folder 299-300)
- University of California, Merced - Building Research Partnerships Program, 2016-2017 (Box 47, Folder 301)
- University of Chicago - China, Art, History: New Orientations Conference, Wu Hung, 2016-2017 (Box 47, Folder 302)
- University of Chicago - Tianlongshan Caves Project, 2015-2017 (Box 47, Folder 303)
- University of Denver - Religion and Social Cohesion in Conflict-Affected Countries, 2012-2019 (Box 48, Folder 304-305)
- University of Iowa - Chinese as a Second Language, 2008-2018 (Box 48, Folder 306-307)
- University of Iowa Museum of Art - Environmental Impact on the Electronic Industry in China and the United States Documentary, 2013-2017 (Box 48, Folder 308)
- University of Michigan - Women's and Gender Studies Workshops, Fudan University, Shanghai, 2010-2018 (Box 49, Folder 309)
- University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Islamic Political Parties after the Arab Spring, 2010-2018 (Box 49, Folder 310-311)
- University of Pennsylvania - Digital Library of Northern Thai Manuscripts Project, 2013-2018 (Box 49, Folder 312)
- University of Southern California - Summer Kambun Workshop, 2013-2018 (Box 49, Folder 313)
- University of Southern California - Innovating International Religion Coverage: Collaboration between Scholars and Practitioners, 2012-2017 (Box 50, Folder 314-315)
- University of Southern California - Center for Transpacific Studies, 2011-2018 (Box 50, Folder 316-317)
- University of Virginia - Hearth to Hearth Religious Conflict Transformation in the Middle East, Dr. Peter Ochs, 2013-2018 (Box 50, Folder 318)
- University of Washington - Myanmar Librarian Training Consortium, 2015-2017 (Box 51, Folder 319)
- University of Washington, ADVANCE Center for Institutional Change - Interrupting Bias in the Faculty Search Process: A Film and Facilitation Guide, 2009-2011 (Box 51, Folder 320)
- Urban Affairs Coalition - Institute for Southeast Asian Archaeology, Joyce White, 2017-2018 (Box 51, Folder 321)
- USA Committee for UNESCO - General Support, 2003-2006 (Box 51, Folder 322)
- Vassar College - "Embodying Compassion in Buddhist Art: Image, Pilgrimage, Practice" Exhibition and Catalog, 2014-2017 (Box 51, Folder 323)
- Vermont Studio Center - Chinese Poetry and Translation Residency Program, 2012-2018 (Box 51, Folder 324)
- Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - "Jasper Johns and Edvard Munch: Love, Loss, and the Cycle of Life" Exhibition and Catalog, 2015-2018 (Box 51, Folder 325)
- Volunteers in Asia (VIA) - Burma/Myanmar Program, 2011-2014 (Box 52, Folder 326)
- Walker Art Center - "Allen Ruppersberg: Intellectual Property 1968-2018" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2019 (Box 52, Folder 327)
- Washington County Museum of Fine Arts - 20th Century American Art Collection, 2013-2017 (Box 52, Folder 328)
- Weatherspoon Art Museum - Permanent Collection Storage System, 2013-2019 (Box 52, Folder 329)
- Women in Engineering ProActive Network, Inc. (WEPAN) - Knowledge Center, 2010-2015 (Box 52, Folder 330)
- Women in Engineering ProActive Network, Inc. (WEPAN) - Clare Boothe Luce Program, 2008-2013 (Box 52, Folder 331)
- Women in Engineering ProActive Network, Inc. (WEPAN) - General Support, 2003-2011 (Box 52, Folder 332)
- WGBH Educational Foundation - Politics and Theology of the Sunn-Shia'a Divide FRONTLINE Program, 2017-2018 (Box 52, Folder 333)
- WGBH Educational Foundation - Extraordinary Women Engineers Initiative, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 334)
- White House Historical Association - Digitize the American Art and Architecture Collections, 2013-2017 (Box 53, Folder 335-336)
- Whitney Museum of American Art - "Grant Wood" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2019 (Box 53, Folder 337)
- Williams College Museum of Art - Digitization of the American Art Collection, 2014-2017 (Box 53, Folder 338)
- Wings Over the Rockies Air and Space Museum - Latina/Latino STEM Summit, 2016-2019 (Box 53, Folder 339)
- Wings Over the Rockies Air and Space Museum - Educational Programs, Peter Luce, 2014-2019 (Box 53, Folder 340)
- Woodmere Art Museum - Violet Oakley Collection and Resource Center, 2017-2021 (Box 53, Folder 341)
- Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars - Chinese Foreign Policy Documents Database, Cold War International History Policy, 2015-2017 (Box 54, Folder 342)
- Worcester Art Museum - Decorative Arts Galleries, Curatorial Assistant (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2021 (Box 54, Folder 343)
- Yale University Art Gallery - Storage of American Art Collection and Archives, West Campus Collection Studies Center, 2014-2018 (Box 54, Folder 344)
- Yale University Art Gallery - "Rhode Island Furniture, 1650-1830" Exhibition and Catalog, 2013-2017 (Box 54, Folder 345)